<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ishmeet Grewal</title>
    <link>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ishmeet Grewal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://ishmeetgrewal.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My First 10K</title>
      <link>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/my-first-10k/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/my-first-10k/</guid>
      <description>I ran my first 10K race today at the 2015 Panerathon in Youngstown, OH. The following describes how it went.
Pro-tip: Don&amp;rsquo;t eat a full pizza AND Chipotle the night before running a race.
 Mile 0: Blast off to the bass drop of Calvin Harris&amp;rsquo;s Sweet Nothing Remix Mile 0 - 1: Pew, pew, pew, I keep passing people. Such slowpokes. This is fun. Clock fastest mile time at 7:34.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Backpacking Through Life</title>
      <link>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/backpacking-through-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/backpacking-through-life/</guid>
      <description>This year has been good to me. I have visited three countries and stepped on another continent. I have met a lot of new people and made some great new friends. Many new experiences have enriched my life and given me a better perspective of the world, of people, and of myself.
Why did I write this? Now that you&amp;rsquo;ve read the first paragraph, clearly, I know everything about the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honduras</title>
      <link>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/honduras/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/honduras/</guid>
      <description>I participated in an Engineering Service-Learning course through OSU where we traveled to Honduras over Spring Break 2015 and implemented sustainable engineering solutions for an orphanage.
Montaña de Luz (Mountain of Light), is an orphanage for children with HIV/AIDS. Founded in 2000 as a Hospice, the orphanage has now become a loving home providing hope for these children thanks to the availability of anti-retroviral mediactions. Located an hour and half to the East of Tegucigalpa on top of a mountain overlooking a valley of small towns and sugar cane fields the mountain of light is a refuge for children who desperately need the specialized care, nurturance, healing and love provided to them in this refuge from a world where AIDS is stigmatizing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Costa Rica</title>
      <link>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/costa-rica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/costa-rica/</guid>
      <description>I spent 10 days in Costa Rica with a group on a Service-Adventure trip through Buck-I-SERV at OSU. This ended up being mostly an adventure trip. We started off by hiking seven miles into the rainforest where we spent five days staying with homestays, helping out with daily tasks, and maintaining trails. Along the way, we went caving, waterfall rappelling, tree climbing, and whitewater rafting, along with a LOT of hiking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sikhism - The Tenets</title>
      <link>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/sikhism-tenets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/sikhism-tenets/</guid>
      <description>Sikhism is the 5th largest religion in the world and has been around since the 15th century. The Holy Book of Sikhism, known as Sri Guru Granth Sahib, is composed of 1,430 pages and contains the teachings of the ten Gurus on how to live a just and virtuous life. That is a lot of pages to read and understand. However, the essence of the message of Sikhism can truly be found in just the first nine phrases of the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi Timelapse</title>
      <link>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/raspberry-pi-timelapse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/raspberry-pi-timelapse/</guid>
      <description>This weekend, Byers Imports unveiled the new Jaguar F-Type Coupe and invited people to autocross for free. I set up a Raspberry Pi at the start line to record a picture every 10 seconds. It managed to capture every car that autocrossed and a pretty cool view of the moving clouds.
  Connect the camera The folks over at Raspberry Pi have created a nice tutorial of how to setup the camera and connect it to Pi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manual Transmission</title>
      <link>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/manual-transmission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/manual-transmission/</guid>
      <description>Over the past year, I have gradually developed an avid interest in automobiles. Before that, my fascination with cars only extended to the aesthetics. However, after regularly racing go karts this summer and getting hooked on watching Formula 1, I have also come to appreciate the performance of vehicles. In order to understand these beautiful beasts, I am writing a series on the basics of an automobile in order to get an introductory understanding of the involved mechanics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skydiving</title>
      <link>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/skydiving/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/skydiving/</guid>
      <description>In order to cross off another thing off my Impossible List, I went skydiving today. I’m not too big on large men strapped to my back with our pelvic regions in close proximity, so I chose to go the Accelerated Free Fall (AFF) route. Start Skydiving in Middletown, OH, the number 1 dropzone in the world, offers the First Jump Course for people who want to learn the basics of skydiving and may want to pursue a license in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jet Engines</title>
      <link>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/jet-engines/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/jet-engines/</guid>
      <description>I love to travel. Have you figured that out yet? My passion for travelling takes me to new cities, countries, and continents. I usually fly to places, but I didn’t know how a jet engine works to take me to new destinations. Since I will be working at GE Aviation this summer, I decided to figure out how a jet engine works.
GE Aviation, the builder of the best jet engines in the world, did an excellent job in creating this interactive explanation of how jet engines function.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ishmeetgrewal.com/p/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago, I had a startling revelation – I don’t actually know how most of the world works. Of course, I understand math concepts and I know that human beings need oxygen to live. But what about WiFi? 4G LTE? The contact lenses I rely on everyday? From complicated systems like the New York City Subway to trivial things like scotch tape, I have absolutely no clue how numerous things function and enable me to live my comfortable lifestyle.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
